lifespanfitness.com 2012-05-10

# LifeSpan Fitness | Policies

## Privacy Policy

PCE Health & Fitness ("PCE"), maker of LifeSpan fitness equipment, is committed to ensuring your privacy and protecting your identity. This privacy policy describes how we handle the personal information you provide on this website.

PCE collects personal information from the ordering and registration processes, and from communications you initiate with us. PCE keeps all online customer information confidential, and does not sell or exchange customer information with other companies. PCE discloses personal information only to reputable vendors who assist us in processing information or fulfilling customer orders. These vendors are restricted from using the information for any purpose other than to help us provide products and services. Occasionally PCE may contact you about new features or products which may be of interest to you, or request your written consent to use some information for marketing or promotional purposes.

In addition to information you provide, PCE utilizes technology to track behaviors as customers navigate through our website. Like most companies operating on the internet, we collect data about the areas you visit on this website and the technology you use. We do not gather or use any specific personal information about persons using this site. PCE uses this information to enhance the operations of this website, by determining which areas of the website are most useful and popular, and which areas may need improvement. We also use the information for security purposes to provide you a safe online environment.

This website contains links for your convenience to other websites. These third party websites operate independently and PCE does not control these sites.

Your privacy and security are very important to PCE. The technology and processes we use maintain the integrity and security of our databases. All data is stored on an access-controlled secured server, with credit card information stored only temporarily until the order is complete. Information is used solely to support your order, to ensure you are satisfied with your purchase, and to ensure we provide you the best products and information you need to live a healthy life.

Please e-mail comments or questions about our policies to [info@lifespanfitness.com](mailto:info@lifespanfitness.com) or write to:

PCE Health and Fitness  
785 West 1700 South, Suite 1  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84014

## Delivery

Most products are delivered to customers within seven to ten business days in the contiguous 48 United States. Orders placed online and shipped in the state of Utah incur a 6.85% sales tax charge. An additional cost may be incurred for expedited orders or for orders delivered to rural areas. For orders placed on [www.LifeSpanFitness.com](http://www.lifespanfitness.com/), shipping and delivery is currently not available to Alaska, Hawaii, Canada or other countries. Authorized LifeSpan retailers in your country, if available, can assist you. Call (877) 654-3837 option 2 for assistance in locating a retailer. Deliveries for products purchased at a LifeSpan authorized retailer adhere to the retailer's policies.

Products are shipped either by UPS or by freight carrier. UPS shipments follow standard UPS protocol. If your product is shipped via freight carrier, such as R&L Carriers, you will be contacted by phone to schedule a delivery time. You will receive email notification informing you of your shipment, and you can also check the status of your shipment by contacting LifeSpan shipping at (877) 654-3837 x105 and providing your invoice number. Learn more about our Free Shipping and Additional Delivery Services.

In the event PCE delivers an item for which you paid for but refuse, you may be required to pay a 20% restocking fee and all shipping charges for transportation from and to PCE.

## Guarantee and Return Policy

PCE guarantees full satisfaction of the products we sell. Returning an item depends on where you purchased the item. If you purchased a product from a retailer or from another website, please contact the retailer or site for instructions about returns. For products purchased directly from this site, contact PCE by e-mailing [info@lifespanfitness.com](mailto:info@lifespanfitness.com) for proper written authorization/approval prior to returning the item. To be eligible for a full refund or credit, you must contact PCE in writing within 30 days of receiving delivery of your purchased item. No returns will be accepted without prior written authorization from PCE. Items must be returned in good condition and in original packaging within 10 business days of receiving written authorization from PCE. You must prepay shipping and handling charges and either insure the shipment or assume responsibility for risk of loss or damage during shipment. Return pick-ups are scheduled during normal business hours only. PCE will credit your purchase using the original form of payment immediately upon receipt of the returned item.

## How It Works

  1. Select the product that you wish to purchase and click "Add to Cart"
  2. Once shopping has been completed, click "Proceed to Checkout"
  3. Enter the shipping information to where the product, part, accessory and/or warranty will be shipped
  4. Enter the billing information and credit card information using our secure SSL server
  5. Review the entered shipping and billing information, once correct click "Complete Purchase"
  6. Once your order has been received you will receive a confirmation e-mail from LifeSpan Fitness providing your entered information and invoice number
  7. Within 72 hours of placing the order you will be contacted by either the local authorized retailer or carrier that will be providing the appropriate product handling. All accessories, parts and/or extended warranty agreements will be shipped via UPS Ground or USPS Priority, unless designated differently during the purchase
  8. Products will be delivered in 7-10 business days
  9. Please call Customer Service at (801) 973-9993 x106 with any questions or comments once you have received your products
  10. Thank you for your purchase!

## Manufacturer's Warranty Policy

Warranty coverage is specific to each product. To register your product for its warranty, customers must register online or complete and mail the warranty card within 30 days of purchase. LifeSpan does not support any warranty purchased through a retailer or online at websites other than [www.LifeSpanFitness.com](http://www.lifespanfitness.com/).

LifeSpan product warranties apply only to the original owner and are non-transferable. This warranty is expressly limited to the repair or replacement of a defective frame, motor, electronic component or defective part and is the sole remedy of the warranty. For customers not located within 50 miles of a LifeSpan Authorized Service provider, LifeSpan will pay up to a maximum of $150.00 towards a service call. This warranty does not cover normal wear and tear, improper assembly or maintenance or installation of parts or accessories not originally intended for the treadmill, bike, rower, stretch partner or elliptical. The warranty does not apply to damage or failure due to accident, abuse, corrosion, discoloration of paint or plastic, or neglect. PCE's responsibility under this warranty is limited to replacing or repairing at PCE's option.
